A Guide to the Records of the Arlington Heritage Alliance, Inc., 1976-2006
Arlington Public Library, Center for Local History
- Audio-Visual Materials
  - Slides
    - Arlington County historic sites, buidlings and houses (Box 20)
      - Courthouse Area, 1991
      - Courthouse Plaza, 1989
      - Days Inn motel at Route 50 and Pershing, 1993
      - Eastman-Fenwick House, c. 1876, at 6733 Lee Highway, 1991
      - Eastman-Fenwick House, c. 1876, at 6733 Lee Highway, 1991
      - Farmhouse, c. 1900, on N. Daniel Street, 1993
      - Fillmore Gardens, c. 1942, on Walter Reed Drive, 1991
      - Fillmore Gardens, c. 1942, on Walter Reed Drive, 1991
      - Fillmore Gardens, c. 1942, on Walter Reed Drive, 1991
      - Fillmore Gardens, c. 1942, on Walter Reed Drive, 1991
      - Fillmore Gardens, c. 1942, on Walter Reed Drive, 1990
      - 2421 24th Street N. in Fort C. F. Smith (c. 1863), 1991
      - 2411 24th Street N. in Fort C. F. Smith (c. 1863), 1991
      - Fort Ethan Allen, c. 1861, at 3829 N. Stafford Street, 1991
      - Fort Ethan Allen, c. 1861, at 3829 N. Stafford Street, 1991
      - Fort Ethan Allen, c. 1861, at 3829 N. Stafford Street, 1991
      - Fort Meyer at Pershing and Route 50, 1991
      - Fort Meyers Heights, 1991
      - George Nicholas Saegmuller, c. 1847, at 511 Little Falls Road and Florida Street, 1991
      - George Nicholas Saegmuller, c. 1847, at 511 Little Falls Road and Florida Street, 1991
      - George Nicholas Saegmuller, c. 1847, at 511 Little Falls Road and Florida Street, 1991
      - Saegmueller House at 511 Little Falls Road, 1992
      - Saegmueller House at 511 Little Falls Road, 1992
      - Glebe House, c. 1820, at 4527 17th Street N., 1991
      - Glebe House, c. 1820, at 4527 17th Street N., 1991
      - Glebe House, c. 1820, at 4527 17th Street N., 1991
      - Glenmore, once a hunting lodge built in 1906, at 3440 N. Roberts Lane, off George Washington Parkway, 1991
      - Harry Crossman House, c. 1892, at 2501 N. Underwood Street, 1991
      - Harry Crossman House, c. 1892, at 2501 N. Underwood Street, 1991
      - Harry Gray House, c. 1881, at 1005 S. Quinn Street, 1991
      - Hume School, 1992
      - Hume School, 1991
      - Iwo Jima and 1960s era high rise, 1991
      - Jacob's Castle, Bay-Eva Castle, 1991
      - Jacob's Castle, 1992
      - Side of Jacob's Castle, 1991
      - Jacob's Castle as seen from the Parkway, 1992
      - Jacob's Castle, 1991
      - Jacob's Castle, "Bayeva", 1991
      - Interior Staircase of Jacob's Castle, 1991
      - Jacob's Castle, 1991
      - Jacob's Castle, 1991
      - Jacob's Castle, 1992
      - Jacob's Castle, 1992
      - Jacob's Castle, 1992
      - Ball Building on Lawyers' Row (negative 20), 1989
      - Rear of the Ball Building on Lawyers' Row, 1990
      - Det. and rubble of the Ball Building on Lawyers' Row, June 1990
      - Jesse Building on Lawyers' Row, 1989
      - Jesse Building on Lawyers' Row, 1989
      - Detail of window on Lawyers' Row, 1989
      - Jesse Building on Lawyers' Row, 1989
      - Rear of Jesse Building on Lawyers' Row, 1990
      - Jesse-Hosmer Building on Lawyers' Row, 1989
      - Moncure Building on Lawyers' Row, 1990
      - Moncure Building on Lawyers' Row, 1989
      - Moncure Building under demolition on Lawyers' Row, 1990
      - Moncure Building on Lawyer's Row (negative 12A), 1989
      - Moncure Building on Lawyers' Row, 1989
      - Moncure Building on Lawyers' Row, 1989
      - Moncure Building on Lawyers' Row, 1989
      - Rucker Building on Lawyers' Row, 1989
      - Rucker Building on Lawyers' Row, 1989
      - Rucker Building on Lawyers' Row
      - Lawyers' Row
      - Lawyers' Row
      - Lee Shopping Center on Pershing Street
      - Lee Shopping Center on Pershing Street
      - Detail of the Lee Shopping Center on Pershing Street
      - Little Tavern on Lee Highway
      - Little Tavern and Pawnbrokers on Lee Highway and Highland
      - Lomax AME Zion Church, c. 1922, at 2704 24th Road S.
      - Lomax AME Zion Church, c. 1922, at 2704 24th Road S.
      - Lothrop House at Wilson Blvd. near Seven Corners
      - Christ Church at 3620 Pershing in Lyon Park
      - Community Center in Lyon Park
      - Community Center in Lyon Park
      - Community Center in Lyon Park
      - Lyon Park World War I monument
      - Modern home at 1725 Danville Street in Lyon Village
      - 1730 Danville Street in Lyon Village
      - Spanish-style home with a modern addition at 2625 18th Street N. in Lyon Village
      - Spanish-style home at 1714 Calvert Street in Lyon Village
      - Community Methodist Church on Key Blvd. in Lyon Village
      - Lyon Village
      - Spanish-style houses at 1406 and 1408 Hancock in Lyon Village
      - 13th Street and Highland in Lyon Village
      - M & M Motors
      - Matthew F. Maury School, c. 1910, at 3550 Wilson Blvd.
      - Matthew F. Maury School, c. 1910, at 3550 Wilson Blvd.
      - 23rd Street & Irving Street in the Maywood Historic District, c. 1900
      - 23rd Street in the Maywood Historic District, c. 1900
      - Maywood Historic District, c. 1900
      - Maywood Historic District, c. 1900
      - Maywood Historic District, c. 1900
      - Maywood Historic District, c. 1900
      - Maywood Historic District, c. 1900
      - Maywood Historic District, c. 1900
      - Maywood Historic District, c. 1900
      - Maywood Historic District, c. 1900
      - Maywood Historic District, c. 1900
      - Maywood Historic District, c. 1900
      - Maywood Historic District, c. 1900
      - Water tower, c. 1910, in Missionhurst
      - Door details and lions made of cast iron at Missionhurst, c. 1910
      - Missionhurst, c. 1910
      - Missionhurst, c. 1910
      - Chapel later added to Missionhurst, c. 1910
      - Detail of the water tower at Missionhurst, c. 1910
      - Motel 50, c. 1958
      - Motel 50, c. 1958
      - Sara Leach Sign for National Pawnbrokers
      - Sara Leach Sign for National Pawnbrokers
      - Sara Leach Sign for National Pawnbrokers
      - Sara Leach Sign for National Pawnbrokers
      - S. 24th Street in Nauck
      - Palisade Gardens
      - Tower Villas and funeral home in Pollard Gardens
      - West facade of the Prospect House, c. 1960s
      - East facade of the Prospect House, c. 1960s
      - Prospect House, c. 1960s
      - Quarterdeck
      - Rosslyn as seen from the Lincoln Memorial
      - Rosslyn
      - Rosslyn
      - Rosslyn
      - Rosslyn
      - Rosslyn
      - The Dancers in Rosslyn, c. 1980s
      - Rosslyn - I.M.
      - Rosslyn
      - N. Quinn Street & Key Blvd. in Rosslyn
      - St. Thomas More Church on Route 50
      - St. Thomas More Church on Route 50
      - Former Sears at Garden Center and Main Street
      - Sears Auto Store on Clarendon Blvd. near Wilson Blvd.
      - Taft Towers
      - Travers Family Graveyard, c. 1830, at 1309 S. Monroe Street
      - Travers Family Graveyard, c. 1830, at 1309 S. Monroe Street
      - Trinity Church, c. 1941
      - Uni-Car Auto Sales
      - Uni-Car Auto Sales
      - W. & O.D. Railroad Regional Park/Bluemont Park on Wilson Blvd.
      - Walker Chapel and Cemetery at 4102 N. Glebe Road
      - Walker Chapel and Cemetery at 4102 N. Glebe Road
      - Walker Chapel and Cemetery at 4102 N. Glebe Road
      - Walker Chapel and Cemetery at 4102 N. Glebe Road
      - Walker Chapel and Cemetery at 4102 N. Glebe Road
      - Westmoreland Terrace
      - Westmoreland Terrace
      - Westmoreland Terrace
      - Westmoreland Terrace
      - Westover Baptist Church
      - Wilson Boulevard
      - Wilson School
      - Wilson Theater, demolished in 1991
      - Wilson Theater, demolished in 1991
      - House adjacent to the Wilson Theater, demolished in 1991
      - Wilson Theater, demolished in 1991
      - Fence near Wilson Theater, demolished in 1991
      - House at N. Fairfax Dr. near Taft
      - House at N. Fairfax Dr. near Taft
      - Cast concrete house, c. 1900
      - Double house on N. Nelson Street
      - Rowhouses on N. Nelson Street near Quincy
      - Spanish Colonial revival House, c. 1930s, on N. Hancock Street
      - House
      - Apartment building at Quinn & Key Blvd.
      - House
      - House
      - House
      - House
      - House
      - House
      - Building
      - Apartment building at 1215 Scott Street and Route 50, under demolition
      - Apartment building at 1215 Scott Street and Route 50, under demolition
      - Apartment building at 1215 Scott Street and Route 50, under demolition
      - Apartment building at 1215 Scott Street and Route 50, under demolition
      - Apartment building on 1240 N. Taft Street, under demolition
      - Apartment building on 1240 N. Taft Street, under demolition
      - Apartment building, c. 1949 on 1240 N. Taft Street
      - Apartment building, c. 1952, on 1215 N. Scott Street
      - Apartment building, c. 1959, at 1910-1912 N. 13th Road
      - Apartment building at Lee Highway & N. Quinn Street
      - Apartment building
      - Apartment building, c. 1954, at 2005 N. Fairfax
      - Apartment building
      - Apartment building
      - Apartment building
      - Apartment building
      - Apartment building
      - Office building
      - View of construction
      - Sign for the Confederate outpost at Bluemont Junction
      - Shopping Center
      - Detail of a shopping center
      - Detail of Flags Seafood in a shopping center
      - Detail of a shopping center
      - Apartment complex
      - Apartment complex
      - A door at an apartment complex
      - Apartment complex
      - View of a staircase at an apartment complex
      - Apartment complex
      - View of the road near an apartment complex
      - Apartment complex
      - A door at an apartment complex
      - Apartment complex
      - Apartment complex
      - Apartment complex
      - Apartment complex
      - Apartment complex
      - Trees
      - Possible view of the Potomac River
      - A bridge
      - Building interior
      - Landscape
      - Group of people
      - Group of people
      - Group of people
      - Group of people with a sign at the Heritage Walk
      - Group of people with a sign during Discover Your Regional Parks
      - Arlandria in Alexandria
      - Exterior of Lustron in Alexandria
      - Detail of the concrete foundation of Lustron in Alexandria
      - Eaves and door roof of Lustron in Alexandria
      - 4121 Mt. Vernon Ave. in Alexandria
      - The Clark House in Fairfax County
  - Photographs
    - AHA Meetings, 1999 (Box 20)
      R175-0439 to 0463
    - Arna Valley Apartments, 2000 (Box 20)
      R175-0464 to 0473
    - Columbia Pike Initiative, 2001 (Box 20)
      R175-0474 to 0500
    - Dawson-Bailey House, 1990 (Box 20)
      R175-0501 to 0511
    - Historic American Building Survey, 1990 ** (Box 20)
      R175-0512 to 0530
    - Jacob's Castle** (Box 20)
      R175-0531 to 0551
    - Lawyers' Row (Historic American Buildings Survey 1277) - Ball, Jesse, and Rucker Buildings, 1990 ** (Box 20)
      R175-0552 to 0571
    - Lawyers' Row (Historic American Buildings Survey 1277) - Moncure, Jesse-Hosner, Lawyers' Row Block and Simmonds Building, 1990 ** (Box 20)
      R175-0572 to 0584
    - Lawyers' Row** (Box 20)
      R175-0585 to 0618
    - Miscellaneous (Box 20)
      R175-0619 to 0645
    - Tour for National Trust, 10/20/99 - photos of Buckingham and Fairlington (Box 20)
      R175-0646 to 0661
    - Vic Muniec, 1995-2001 (Box 20)
      - Fort Ethan Allen, 1995
      - Fort Ethan Allen, 1995
      - Glebe House
      - AHA concern over Dog Yard, November 2000
      - Fort Ethan Allen, Breastworks from inside dog run, December 2000
      - AHA concern over Dog Yard, November 2000
      - Start of demolition of the Garden Apartment Buidlings on Lee Highway, April 2001
      - Science Focus School, April 2001
      - H-B Woodlawn School, 2001
      - Walter Reed Drive & Columbia Pike, April 2001
      - Walter Reed Drive & Columbia Pike, April 2001
      - Walter Reed Drive, one block from Columbia Pike, April 2001
      - Street in back of theaters
      - Knights of Columbus Property, November 1999
      - Knights of Columbus Property, November 1999
      - Rear view of the Knights of Columbus Property
      - Property adjacent to the Knights of Columbus property, November 1999
    - Unidentified** (Box 20)
      R175-0676 to 0713
  - Other formats
    - VHS Tape - Arlington County Board meeting, 2/23/1991, Item 7, VHS tape (Box 20)
    - Floppy Disc - 5" - Buckingham Photo ID's, WP 3.5 (Box 20)
    - Ball Building "Last Chance Party" Pins (Box 20)
    - Business cards, n.d. (Box 20)
- Victor E. Muniec Files
  - American Heritage Alliance materials
    - Agendas, 1990-1996 (incomplete) (Box 21)
    - Annual Report, April 30, 2003 (Box 21)
    - Arlington County Civic Federation, May 4, 1990 (Box 21)
    - Board of Directors [n.d.] (Box 21)
    - Charter Members, 1989-1990 (Box 21)
    - Dawson House, Arlington Heritage Festival, 1990 (Box 21)
    - Ideas, 2002-03 (Box 21)
    - Letters and emails, 1996-2003 (Box 21)
    - Membership Application, 1991 (Box 21)
    - Minutes of Meetings, 1989-1996 (incomplete) (Box 21)
    - Most Endangered Historic Places, June 2, 2003 (Box 21)
    - Newsletters, 1990-2007 (incomplete)* (Box 21)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1989-2007 (Box 21)
    - Planning Notes for Retreat (Box 21)
    - Potential Development-Outreach Projects, February 19, 1990 (Box 21)
    - Programs, 1996 (Box 21)
    - Publications (Box 21)
    - Sample By-Laws and Historic Group Organizational Plans (Box 21)
    - Tour, Arlington Backyard Gardens, 1996, 1998 (Box 21)
    - Tour, Colonial Village, Draft, February 19, 1999 (Box 21)
    - Tour, World of Frank Lyon (Box 21)
    - Website Home Page, 10/23/2003 (Box 21)
  - Arlington County
    - Abingdon Plantation, 1989-2000 (Box 21)
    - Arlington Commission for the Arts, November 8, 1990 (Box 21)
    - Arlington County Deed Books held in Alexandria City (Box 21)
    - Arlington County Fair, August 15-18, 1996 (Box 21)
    - Arlington County, Virginia, Available Space Report, July 1996 (Box 21)
    - Arlington County, Virginia, General Land Use Plan, June 30, 1990 (Box 21)
    - Arlington County, Virginia, Handbook of Planning Terminology, [n.d.] (Box 21)
    - Arlington County, Virginia, Profile, January 1996 (Box 21)
    - The Arlington Environment, Newsletter, Summer 2001 (Box 21)
    - Arlington Historical Society Newsletters, 1990 1990-2003 (incomplete) (Box 21)
    - Arlington Housing Corporation (Box 21)
    - Ashton Heights Civic Association re: Arlington Arts Center, February 6, 1991 (Box 21)
    - Ball-Sellers House, Events, 1999 (Box 21)
    - Ballston, Arlington's New Downtown, map [n.d.] (Box 21)
    - Ballston Partnership's 1998 Directory (Box 21)
    - Ballston Sector Plan, May 1980 (Box 21)
    - Ballston-Virginia Square Neighborhood Conservation Program, October 1984 (Box 21)
    - Ballston-Virginia Square Neighborhood Conservation Plan, Amendment, 1990 (Box 21)
    - Black Heritage Museum of Arlington County, Virginia (Box 22)
    - Bluemont Junction History (Box 22)
    - Bluemont Junction Soccer Field, 1989 (Box 22)
    - Buckingham, Covenant Conditions for Development in Buckingham Villages 4 & 5, Draft, May 25, 1993 (Box 22)
    - Buckingham: National Register of Historic Places, Nomination Form, August 23, 1991 (Box 22)
    - Buckingham Neighborhood Strategy Area Plan, 2000 (Box 22)
    - Buckingham Shopping Center, 1990 (Box 22)
    - Clarendon Commercial District, Preliminary Information Request for the Potential Nomination as a Historic District, April 2001 (Box 22)
    - Clarendon Mid-Course Review-Update, April 5, 1990 (Box 22)
    - Clarendon Sector Plan, Addendum A, May 15, 1990 (Box 22)
    - Clarendon Sector Plan for the Urban Village, Task Force Draft, December 20, 2004 (Box 22)
    - Colonial Village Historic District, Certificate of Appropriateness, 1990 (Box 22)
    - Court House Row, 1986-1989 (Box 22)
    - Fort C.F. Smith, Historic District Designation for the Hendry Estate, March 27, 1986 (Box 22)
    - Fort C.F. Smith Historic District, Application for Certificate of Appropriateness, 1990-1991 (Box 22)
    - Fort C.F. Smith, "A Preservation Plan, Fort C.F. Smith and the Hendry Estate," Wynn E. Witthans, January 1986 (Box 22)
    - Fort Ethan Allen, "Friends of Ft. Ethan Allen," 2002 (Box 22)
    - Forth Ethan Allen, Grant Application to the American Battlefield Protection Program, 2005 (Box 22)
    - Fort Ethan Allen, Grant to Oversee and Manage the Resource Identification for Fort Ethan Allen, 2005-2006 (Box 22)
    - Fort Ethan Allen, "Historical Background & Impact Assessment of Park Activities on the Historic Resources of Fort Ethan Allen Park," prepared by Walton Owen, June 15, 2000 (Box 22)
    - Fort Ethan Allen Programs, 2003-2006 (Box 22)
    - Freedman's Village, 2002-2003 (Box 22)
    - George Mason University in Arlington, 1996 (Box 22)
    - Historic Arlington Roundtable Lunch, January 7, 2003 (Box 22)
    - Jefferson Davis Corridor Land Use Review, Community Workshop, May 1991 (Box 22)
    - Krowne Lustron House, June 20, 2006 (Box 22)
    - Lyon Park, 2000 (Box 22)
    - Maywood, Designation of Maywood Neighborhood Historic District, 1990 (Box 23)
    - Maywood Homeowner's Handbook: Design Guidelines, Draft, January 1990 (Box 23)
    - Maywood Homeowner's Handbook: Design Guidelines, Draft, August 2005 (Box 23)
    - Northern Virginia Regional Parks, [1989] (Box 23)
    - Quincy Park North Walking Tour Meeting, July 27, 2005 (Box 23)
    - Quincy Street, Adhoc Quincy Street Open Space working Group Final Report, November 16, 1992 (Box 23)
    - Quincy Street, Evaluation and Historic Documentation for the Quincy Street Extension Project, July 1992, revised October 1992 (Box 23)
    - Rosslyn-Ballston Corridor, Map, February 2001 (Box 23)
  - Virginia and the Metropolitan DC Area
    - Civil War Sites (Box 23)
    - Historic Huntley, Historic and Architectural Significance, [n.d.] (Box 23)
    - Jamestown, 2007 (Box 23)
    - National World War II Memorial Dedication, May 27-30, 2004 (Box 23)
    - Northern Virginia and Northern Piedmont Networking Meeting, Oatlands Plantation, September 2001 (Box 23)
    - Veterans History Project, Library of Congress, 2004 (Box 23)
    - Virginia Department of Historic Resources, Tourism Handbook, 2001 (Box 23)
    - Virginia Division of Historic Landmarks, Historic District/Brief Survey Form (Box 23)
    - Virginia Highway Historical Markers on African American Virginia History, April 1, 2005 (Box 23)
    - Virginia Historical Sites, Pamphlets (Box 23)
    - The Virginia Landmarks Register, July 1990 (Box 23)
    - Virginia, Newspaper Clippings, 1997 (Box 23)
  - Historic Preservation
    - HALRB Annual Report, 1988 (Box 23)
    - HALRB Meeting, June 19, 1996 (Box 23)
    - HALRB, Minutes, June 19, 1991 (Box 23)
    - HALRB, Agenda, November 28, 2001 (Box 23)
    - HALRB National Register Activity, November 1, 2002 (Box 23)
    - HALRB Preservation Workshop, March 9, 1991 (Box 23)
    - Historic American Buildings Survey, pamphlet [n.d.] (Box 23)
    - Historic Preservation, January/February 1990 (Box 23)
    - National Trust for Historic Preservation Report, Virginia Policies that Contribute to Sprawl: An Agenda for Change, August 2001 (Box 23)
    - Preservation Alliance of Virginia, 2002 (Box 23)
    - Preservation Alliance of Virginia, Preservation and Planning Spring Preservation Workshops, March 29-31, 1990 (Box 24)
    - Preservation Alliance of Virginia, Preservation and Planning Spring Preservation Workshops, March 29-31, 1990, pamphlets (Box 24)
  - Publications
    - "Allie S. Freed and the Buckingham Community Project," by Jonathan P. Kahn-Leavitt, January 21, 1985 (Box 24)
    - American Horticultural Society, Critical Environmental Areas Technique as a Means of Protecting Landscape, Remarks of Thomas W. Richards, [n.d.] (Box 24)
    - Architectural Record, December 1976 (Box 24)
    - Arlington County Historical Magazine, Vol. 9, No. 3, October 1991 (Box 24)
    - Arlington County Historical Magazine, Vol. 10, No. 1, October 1993 (Box 24)
    - Arlington County Historical Magazine, Vol. 10, No. 2, October 1994 (Box 24)
    - "Buckingham: Housing Laboratory," by Oscar Fisher, reprinted from the January 1938 issue of the Architectural Record (Box 24)
    - Chapters from Arlington History, A Series of Reprinted Articles from the Arlington Historical Magazine, 1957-1993, Volume 3: Ballston: Country Crossroads to Urban Village, 1994, (part1) (Box 24)
    - Chapters from Arlington History, A Series of Reprinted Articles from the Arlington Historical Magazine, 1957-1993, Volume 3: Ballston: Country Crossroads to Urban Village, 1994, (part 2) (Box 24)
    - "Colonial Village: The Cultural and Architectural Heritage," by the Colonial Village Preservation Committee, May 25, 1978 (Box 24)
    - "Freedman's Village: Arlington, Virginia, 1863-1900: A book created by the Seventh Grade Students of the H-B Woodlawn Secondary Program," revised second edition, March 1992 (Box 24)
    - Garden Apartments in Arlington, Virginia: Three Preservation Case Studies, by Gail Baker [n.d.] (Box 24)
    - The Illustrious Lustron: A Guide for the Disassembly and Preservation of America's Modern Metal Marvel, by Cynthia Liccese-Torres and Kim A. O'Connell, 2007, [oversized booklet] (Box 24)
    - Lyon Park in Arlington, Virginia: A Suburb of Mail-Order Dreams, by Cynthia Liccese, December 2000 (Box 24)
    - "Lyon Village," by Carolyn V Boaz, Arlington Historical Magazine, October 1993 (Box 24)
    - National Geographic, Vol. 171, No 6, June 1987 (Box 25)
    - The Nature of Things: The Courthouse Row Buildings of Arlington County, Virginia, by Carole E. Hooper [n.d.] (Box 25)
    - The Plaque, Historic Alexandria Foundation, July 1985 (Box 25)
    - Readings in the Geography of Virginia, By Dr. James W. Fonseca, Fall 1995 (Box 25)
    - "The Role of Frank Lyon and his Associates in the Early Development of Arlington County," by Ruth P. Rose, Arlington Historical Magazine, October 1976 (Box 25)
    - Saving the Recent Past, Garden Apartments in Arlington, Virginia, 1999 National Preservation Conference, October 20, 1999 (Box 25)
  - Photographs
    - Lustron House, Final Disassembly, August 2005 - June 2006 (Box 25)
      - Lustron House - Salvage
      - Lustron House Dismantling
      - Lustron House
    - World of Frank Lyon Tour, April 21, 2002 (Box 25)
      - Missionhurst
      - Lyon Village
      - Lyon Park
      - Opening ceremony at Lyon Park Community Center
    - AHA Board Meeting, May 7, 2002 (Box 25)
      - AHA Board meeting at Vic & Judy Muniec's house
    - [Meeting],[n.d.] (Box 25)
    - North Arlington, May 12, 2002 (Box 25)
      - Construction between Washington Boulevard and 10th Street, N.
      - Houses, unidentified
      - CVS at Williamsburg and Little Falls
    - Pollard Gardens, 1994 (Box 25)
      - Pollard Garden Apartments between Arlington Funeral Home and Tower Villa (c. 1994)
    - Fort Ethan Allen, Search for well, August 2005 (Box 25)
      - Search for Well
    - Knee-Wells Renovation Project, 2000-2002 (Box 25)
    - Fort Ethan Allen Walking Tour, May 2002 (Box 25)
    - Colvin Run Mill, March 29, 2002 (Box 25)
    - Ballston Common Mall and Garage, March 2002 (Box 25)
    - Swanson Middle School, February 2002 (Box 25)
    - Reeves House, November 2001 (Box 25)
    - Clarendon Common Market Construction, March 2001 (Box 25)
    - Morning Glory Farm Garden Shop, April 2001 (Box 25)
      - 2300 N. Pershing Dr.
    - Lee Shopping Center, April 2001 (Box 26)
      - N. Pershing Drive
    - Rosslyn, Garden apartments, April 2001 (Box 26)
      - Key Boulevard
    - Glenelg Apartments, April 2001 (Box 26)
      - Lee Highway